If we have a turtle called Amy,
如果我们有一只叫艾米的乌龟
then the statement amy.forward(50) causes that turtle to move forward by 50 pixels.
然后声明 amy.forward (50) 使该海龟向前移动 50 像素
Similarly, amy.back(50) causes the turtle to move backwards by 50 pixels.
同样  Amy.back(50) 使海龟向后移动 50 像素
One thing that's important to understand when writing
有一件事在写作时很重要
turtle programs is that the directions are all from the turtles perspective.
海龟的程式 方向都是从海龟的角度出发
This can be a little bit confusing at
这可能有点让人困惑
first when you tell the turtle to turn left or right.
当你告诉海龟左转或右转时
At any point in the program,
在节目的任何时候
the turtle is facing in a particular direction.
乌龟正朝着特定的方向前进
When you tell the turtle to turn left by 45,
当你告诉海龟左转 45
you're telling it to turn left by 45 degrees from the direction it's currently facing.
你告诉它要从它目前所面对的方向左转 45 度
So, if we want the turtle to draw a square,
所以如果我们想让海龟画个方形
we have to tell it to go forward 100 pixels,
我们得告诉它前进 100 像素
then turn left by 90 degrees from its perspective,
然后从它的角度左转 90 度
forward 100, left 90,
前 100  左 90
forward 100, left 90, forward 100,
前 100  左 90  前 100
and now it's back to where it started although it's facing in a different direction now.
现在又回到了它开始的地方
This can sometimes get a little confusing.
这有时会引起一些混乱
For example, if you want to draw a triangle like this,
比如 如果你想画一个这样的三角形
you might be thinking of having the turtle turn by
你可能会想让海龟
these angles inside the triangle which are 60 degrees.
三角形里面有 60 度角
But actually, you want to have the turtle turn by these angles which are 120 degrees.
但实际上 你想让海龟以 120 度的角度转动
Of course, if you get confused or if you're not quite sure,
当然如果你糊涂了或者你不太确定
you can always experiment.
你总是能做实验
Don't be afraid to try different angles to see what results you'll get.
不要害怕尝试不同的角度去看你会得到什么结果